We have a plan, because of the power of our military, where every bridge in Iran will be decimated by 12 o'clock tomorrow night,
where every power plant in Iran will be out of business, burning, exploding, and never to be used again.
I mean, complete demolition by 12 o'clock, and it'll happen over a period of four hours if we wanted to.
We don't want that to happen.
We may even get involved with helping them rebuild their nation.
And you know what?
If that's the case, the last thing we want to do is start with power plants, which are among the most expensive things, and bridges.
You saw the bridge.
The bridge one.
We were very close to a deal.
And then I got a call from Mr. Whitcoff, Mr. Kushner, and J.D. saying, I think they're breaking the deal.
I said, tell them that's okay, don't worry about it, but tell them to look out their window and watch.
And within 45 minutes, I gave the order to knock out the biggest bridge.
I gave the order to knock out the biggest bridge in, I believe, the Middle East, but the biggest bridge in Iran.
And within 10 minutes after I gave that order, that bridge was over.
So, do I want to do that?
No.
Do I want to destroy their infrastructure?
It will take them 100 years to rebuild.
Right now.
We left today.
Help from the head.
Small, don't say.
We're talking that shit.
And keeping it real.
Small, don't say.
Me and Nana Seals.
So funky.
Bye.